作为美国人  我们不仅有权利
As Americans, we don't just have the right
反对种族歧视和不公正行为
to protest racism and injustice.
我们有这个义务
We have the duty.
但当贾马尔·塔特和克里斯·泰勒下跪
But when Jamal Tate and Chris Taylor took a knee
自由
来反对警方暴力的时候
to protest police violence,
他们被禁赛了
they were suspended.
他们无法禁止我们的言论自由
They cannot suspend our freedom of speech
还有我们抗议的权利
and our freedom to protest.
丹尼·伍兹的女儿组织了反警察示威
Denny Woods' daughter running an anti-police demonstration.
我觉得真是讽刺的定义
I think that's the actual definition of irony.
厉害了
Amazing.
种族歧视是美国特色
Racism is so American--
当我们抗议种族歧视的时候
That when we protest racism,
有些人觉得我们就是在抗议美国
some people think we protest America.
但抗议不公正行为
But protesting injustice,
才是在抗议美国
that's what the flag stands for.
我很不喜欢这个孩子
I got no respect for this kid.
我有六个朋友为国捐躯了
I got six friends who died for that flag.
看到大卫·迪克森了吗
Any sign of David Dixon?
还没有
Nothing yet.
我大老远过来可不是来集会的
I didn't come all this way to get herded like cattle.
-你从哪来  -巴特克里市
- Where you from? - Battle Creek.
大卫·迪克森的老乡
You mean where David Dixon's from?
没错
Yeah. That's right.
-你是大卫的粉丝吗  -我是吗
- You a follower of David's? - Am I?
如果白人今天不划条线
If white men don't draw a line today,
明天我们就不存在了
tomorrow we won't exist.
-我是布莱恩·沃尔什  -阿莫斯
- I'm Brian Walsh. - Amos.
看到迪克森了  他刚到
Got eyes on Dixon. He just got here.
那边的那些人  他们讨厌我的国家对吗
Those people over there, they hate our country, huh?
不尊重我们的警察  我们的国旗对吗
Disrespecting our police, disrespecting our flag, right?
我要问的是  那我们还等什么
And my question to you is, what are we waiting for, huh?
我们行动起来
Let's go do something about it!
我们走  走
Let'go, let's go. Come on.
注意  这些家伙开始行动了
Heads up, these guys are on the move,
朝你们那边过去了
heading your way.
你们不配叫自己美国人
You don't deserve to call yourself an American.
没错
That's right.
听到我说的话了吧
You heard what I said.
去领你妈的救济款吧
Go get your mom's welfare check, boy.
快去啊  听到了吗
Come on. You heard me?
怎么  你想干什么
So, what's up? What you wanna do?
你耳朵里塞了西瓜吗  小子
You got watermelon in your ears, boy?
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我帮你
I got you.
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   Lynn_宁   H小欠
注意  这里是芝加哥警署
Attention, this is the Chicago Police Department.
请立即离开这里
you are hereby ordered to leave this area immediately.
翻译     小萝莉   西之   圈圈
拒绝离开的人
Anyone failing to disperse
校对     圈圈
会被立刻拘留
will be subject to immediate arrest.
我重复一遍  拒绝离开的人
I repeat. Anyone who fails to disperse
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
会被立刻拘留
will be subject to arrest.
后期     8T
目前逮捕了29个人  骚乱斗殴
29 arrests so far, disorderly and battery,
迪克森不在里面
Dixon isn't one of them.
我们清理好这个区域了
We finished sweeping the area.
没看到迪克森
No sign of Dixon.
总监     圈圈
21区的小组  我们接到多个报警电话称
Units at 21, we have multiple calls of shots fired
芝加哥大学西停车场发生枪击案
at the CCU West parking structure.
-西边  -不知道第几层
- West. - Floor unknown.
尸体
Body.
5021紧急情况
5021 emergency.
我是情报组的安东尼奥·道森
This is Antonio Dawson of Intelligence.
我需要封锁整个校园
I need the entire campus on lockdown.
枪杀案凶手在逃  现场有具尸体
We have an active shooter and one dead body.
黑人男性  20来岁
He's a black male, 20's.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十四集
确定是之前下跪的篮球选手
I believe he's the basketball player that was kneeling.
克里斯·泰勒
Chris Taylor.
一枪打中心脏  没有目击者
One shot to the heart, no witnesses.
巡逻警和特警清理了那个区域
Tact, Patrol, SWAT swept the area.
凶手不见了
Shooter's in the wind.
和学校安保聊一聊
Talk to Campus Security.
-拿监控资料  -好
- Get surveillance. - Yeah.
今天这里有很多人  总有人看到什么
A lot of people here today. Somebody saw something.
我们知道大卫·迪克森和克里斯·泰勒
Well, we know David Dixon and Chris Taylor
是先动手的
got into a fist fight.
引发了整场斗殴  我们找不到迪克森
It set this whole thing off. We can't find Dixon.
我刚发短信给鲁塞克
Man, I'm texting Ruzek now.
他说他还在卧底
He said he's still working undercover
跟密歇根的那个帮派
with that gang in Michigan.
让他按兵不动
Tell him to stay under.
说不定能找到迪克森
Maybe get a lead on Dixon.
警长
Sergeant?
刚和布里安娜·伍兹聊完
I just talked to Brianna Woods.
她可能看到了什么
She may have seen something.
-好  -好  谢谢
- Yeah. - Okay, thanks.
布里安娜  好久不见
Hey, Brianna. It's been a while.
我是汉克·博伊特
I'm Hank Voight.
我记得你是谁
I remember who you are.
你们会找出凶手吗
So y'all gonna find out who did this?
你有什么有帮助的信息吗
Well, you got anything that might help us?
没有
No.
整件事都失去控制了
I mean, this whole thing just went off the tracks.
贾马尔
Jamal.
队员们都去见牧师了
The team is meeting with the chaplain.
教练  我去不了
Coach, I can't.
-我得留在这里  -不  去吧
- I gotta stay here. - No, go ahead.
没事  你的队友需要你
It's fine. Your team needs you.
你确定吗
You sure?
我们带你去看医生吧  好吗
Let's get you to a doctor, okay?
来吧
Come on.
听着  我们只想问你几个问题  好吗
Listen, we just wanna ask you a few questions, all right?
-我知道流程  -好
- I know the drill. - All right.
在示威上你看到克里斯打架了吗
You saw Chris get into a fight at the demonstration?
看到了  和那些新纳粹之一
Yeah. One of those Neo-nazis.
跟克里斯说他要杀了他
Told Chris he was gonna kill him.
-这个人吗  -对
- This guy? - That's the one.
你们抓到他了吗
Did you--Did you catch him?
没有  我们还在找他
No, we're still looking.
你有什么关于克里斯的消息吗
Listen, is there anything we should know about Chris?
我们曾经是朋友
We were friends.
大一的时候我就认识他了
I've known him since we were freshmen.
通过他认识了贾马尔
That's how I met Jamal.
贾马尔是你男朋友吗
Jamal is your boyfriend?
对
Yeah.
我写了关于他们的文章
I wrote the article about them.
什么文章
Which article?
两个朋友表明立场
Two friends take a stand.
克里斯和贾马尔出身的社区很糟糕
Chris and Jamal came from a tough neighborhood.
抓住机会念了好大学
Got the golden ticket to a fancy college,
他们就开始抗议
and then they started protesting the anthem.
啦啦队  粉丝  教练
The boosters, the fans, the coaches,
他们不开心
they were not happy.
他们受到威胁了吗
They were getting threats?
外面仇恨太多
There was just so much hate out there.
-他们成了象征  -警长
- They became a symbol. - Sergeant.
我希望这些警官
I hope these officers
很尊重你
are treating you with respect.
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
-医生看过了吗  -嗯
- Doctor take a look at that? - Yeah.
医生说没事
Said it was fine.
听说你陷入了混战
I heard you jumped into the fray.
忍不住
Couldn't help it.
本性难移
Well, some things don't change.
还好有警察在
You're lucky the police were there.
控制不住自己吗
Couldn't resist, huh?
警长  我们能谈谈吗
Sarge, can we talk?
我知道我们俩之前有些不和
I know you and I have our differences.
但这是她的事
But this is about her.
我们必须摒弃前嫌
All that crap needs to be left behind.
我们得赶在演化成种族暴乱之前解决这场凶案
We need to solve this murder before it sparks a race riot.
克里斯·泰勒在大学是控球后卫
Chris Taylor was a point guard at CCU.
野百本地的孩子
Local kid from the Wild Hundreds.
他还很聪明
Smart kid, too.
他的专业是政治科学  绩点为3.5
He was pulling 3.5 as a Political Science major.
在附近有没有什么前科
Any priors from the neighborhood?
有一次  他因为在高中非法持枪
One. He got popped for a possession
被抓到过一次  做了社区服务
in high school, he did community service,
之后没有记录
he was clean after that.
布里安娜说克里斯因为国歌抗议
Brianna said Chris was getting threats
收到过威胁
for anthem protests.
好好核实校园安保  社交媒体
All right, well check Campus Security, social media,
看看有没有什么值得注意的威胁
see if any threats are credible.
在网上针对黑人运动员发布威胁的人中
The one person we know was blogging threats
我们所知的有大卫·迪克森
against black athletes was David Dixon.
联调局本来就因仇恨罪在关注迪克森
Dixon's been on the FBI's radar for hate crimes.
他在印第安纳州因殴打一名移民被捕
He got busted beating an immigrant in Indiana.
他将他打到颅骨骨折住院
Put him in the hospital with a skull fracture.
因为受害人被驱逐出境  所以没有庭审
Never went to trial because the victim got deported.
迪克森和克里斯在集会时产生争执
Dixon and Chris got into a fight at the rally,
迪克森现在仍不知所踪
and Dixon's still in the wind.
鲁塞克还在卧底这些人吗
Hey, is Ruzek still under with these guys?
据我们所知是的
As far as we know.
我刚找校园安保核实过了
Okay, I just finished with Campus Security.
有点发现
I got something.
这是克里斯被杀时的时间线
This is a basic timeline of Chris' murder.
从10点42分开始  这是10点47分
It starts at 10:42. This is 10:47.
这是迪克森
And there's Dixon.
这是十分钟后另一个摄像头的画面
Now, this is a different camera ten minutes later.
两分钟后
Two minutes after that...
看不清他的脸
Can't see his face.
是的  但你能看清他的外套
Yeah, but you can see his jacket.
看起来和迪克森的很像
I mean, it looks a lot like Dixon's.
找到这家伙
Let's find this guy.
我们已经找到他了  警长
We already got him, Sarge.
鲁塞克五分钟之前抓到了这个家伙
Ruzek arrested his Alt-Right ass five minutes ago.
很好  和他聊聊吧
Good, let's have a talk with him.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我们是在为你们而战
We were fighting for your side.
我们是专业的警察
We're pro police, man.
那我告诉你我有什么不明白的
Yeah, well, I'll tell you what I don't get.
我不明白什么白人至上
I don't get this whole white supremacy thing.
根据你的记录
I mean, judging from your record--
你的...
your, uh...
你对社会的贡献
your contribution to society--
除了殴打移民
Aside from beating up immigrants
发布仇恨
and blogging a bunch of hate,
你感觉有什么至上的
why exactly do you feel superior?
我没有  所以我不是白人至上主义者
I don't. That's why I'm not a white supremacist.
我是个白人民族主义者
I'm a white nationalist.
疯了吧
Come on.
人们应该住在自己的部落中
People were meant to live with their own tribes.
说这种话一点都没错
There's nothing wrong with saying that aloud.
你和我
You and me.
我们是一个部落的
We're the same tribe.
可能是一个肤色  但不是一个部落
The same color, maybe. Not same tribe.
好吧
All right, well,
那向我解释一下  警官
then explain something to me, officer.
黑人能穿着写"黑人之力"的衣服
Black man can wear a shirt that says, "Black Power."
女人可以穿写着"女子力"的衣服
Lady wear a shirt that says, "Female Power."
但如果我穿着一件写着"白人之力"的衣服
But if I wear a shirt that says, "White Power,"
我就是种族主义者
I'm a racist.
大卫·迪克森
David Dixon.
兄弟
My brother.
-你好吗  -我很好
- How you doing today? - I'm good.
是吗
Yeah?
很喜欢你的博客
Big fan of your blog.
不过戾气太重了
A lot of anger, though.
根据你说的
I mean, according to your words,
你来芝加哥是为了
you came to the city of Chicago with intentions
掀起种族暴乱
on starting a race riot.
我来芝加哥是为了
I came to Chicago to exercise
首次行使我的言论自由权
my first amendment right of free speech.
言论自由  听着
Hmm, free speech. Now, listen.
我对宪法了解的不多
I don't really know too much about the Constitution
但我了解言论
but I know free speech.
那可不是谋杀
And it ain't homicide.
-伙计们  那不是我干的  -好吧  但这是你
- Guys, that wasn't me. - Okay, but this is you.
那看上去也很像你
And that looks like you, too.
在年轻的克里斯·泰勒被枪杀时
Following the young Chris Taylor into the garage
-跟着他进入车库  -不是我干的
- where he was shot to death. - Not by me.
大卫  我知道你喜欢第一修正案
David, I know you like that first amendment.
就我对你这种兄弟的了解
And if I know anything about brothers like yourself,
你大爱第二修正案
you love the second amendment.
我不喜欢赌博
I'm not a gambling man,
但我敢打赌你肯定有一把枪
but I would bet that you own a gun.
-对吧  -好吧  好吧
- Right? - All right, all right.
你...
Could--
怎么了  大卫  你有一把枪吧
What's wrong, Dave? You own a gun, right?
好吧  我是跟着他
All right, yeah. I did follow him.
-要杀了他  -不
- To kill him. - Nope.
不  我是想揍他一顿
No, I was gonna give him a beat down.
因为他唱国歌时下跪
Because he took a knee for the national anthem?
因为他不尊重我们的国家
Because he disrespected our country.
我的兄弟  我的叔叔
I got a brother, I got a uncle,
我的两个侄子都在军队  那面旗帜
I got two cousins in the Army, and that flag,
对我们来说意味着一切
that means everything to us.
没错
Exactly.
所以你跟着年轻的克里斯·泰勒进入车库
So you followed a young Chris Taylor into that garage.
没错  等我进去时
Yeah, and then when I got there,
我听到一声枪响
I heard a gun go off,
看到一个人跑走了
and I saw a man come running out.
你猜怎么着
And guess what?
那是个黑人
It was a black man.
-是个黑人  -没错
- It was a black man, huh? - That's right.
你显然不是黑人
Well...well, you obviously ain't color blind.
能描述他的身高体重和年纪吗
You got a height, weight, and age for him?
不  我只知道他是黑人
No, all I know is he was black.
但是你们不愿意相信一个白人  对吧
But y'all don't wanna believe a white guy, do you?
我只想知道真相
I just want the truth.
不管是什么颜色的
I don't care what color it is.
好吧
Yeah, well,
事实是  你们可以让我沉默
truth is you can silence me,
但其他相信我们事业的人
but others who believe in the cause,
他们会继续战斗下去
they're gonna continue to fight.
兄弟
Brother.
你朋友的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about your friend.
谢谢
I appreciate it.
我看到你也在抗议现场
I saw you at the demonstration.
免得你多想  你不够格加入反法西斯行动
In case you're wondering, you don't pass for antifa.
我知道警察的思维模式
I know how cops think.
你只是知道你父亲的思维
You know how your father thinks, maybe.
我肯定你对那些在国旗仪式上
I'm sure you've got no sympathy for athletes
对国旗下跪的运动员并不同情
who kneel for the anthem.
好吧  说真的
All right, to be honest,
我甚至不知道人们为什么还要下跪
I don't know why people are kneeling anymore at all.
这算是言论自由吗
I mean, is it about freedom of speech?
是因为总统吗
Is it about the President?
这是关于警察
It's about the police.
是关于针对黑人的执法暴力
It's about violence against black men.
那为什么对国旗不敬
Then why disrespect the flag?
不  你错了
No, you're wrong.
下跪其实是表达尊敬的动作
Kneeling is actually a sign of respect.
不管下不下跪
Kneeling, not kneeling--
我都觉得改变不了什么
I don't think it's gonna change anything.
只会给这座城市带来更多暴力
It's bringing more violence to the city.
而这是我们最不想要的
It's the last thing we need.
趴下  趴下
Get down, get down!
-你中枪了吗  -没  我没事
- Are you hit? - No, I'm okay.
待在这里  不要动
All right, stay here. Don't move.
G5021  上报一个车牌号
5021 George. I got a plate for you.
74PNT97
74 Paul Nora Tom 97.
对警察开枪  黑色牧马人
Shots fired at the police. Black Jeep Wrangler.
他们朝南去了  南国王大道4600号
They're headed southbound, 4600 South King Drive.
我看见了车牌  但我没看到枪手
I got the plate, but I didn't see the shooter.
他就是想当场杀了我们
He had us dead to rights.
那他的枪法够烂的
Eh, he was a piss poor shot.
又或者是想恐吓我们
Or he's just trying to scare us.
有目击者吗
Any other witnesses?
还没发现  还在找
No, not yet. We're still looking.
鉴证科正在鉴定弹壳
Crime techs are processing some of the shell casings.
好  做个弹道检测报告出来
All right, get them to ballistics.
丹尼
Denny.
汉克
Hey, Hank.
你确定你什么都没看见吗
So you're sure you didn't see anything?
我只看见是一辆黑车
All I saw was a black car.
一切都发生得非常快
It happened really fast.
老爸  我有点怕了
Dad, I'm kinda freaked out.
你当然怕  但不会有事的  亲爱的
Of course you are. But you're okay, sweetheart.
他们只是想吓吓你  好吗
Hey, they were just trying to scare you, all right?
给她住处安排辆警车
Put a car at her place.
那你去哪
Where are you going?
我还要去市长办公室
I gotta go to the Mayor's office.
他有点担心局面会失控
He's, uh, worried this thing might spin out of control.
-你不会有事的  -我们会照顾好她
- You're good. - She's in good hands.
警长  我们查到了一辆
Yo, Sarge, I think we got a hit
和那辆黑色牧马人吉普匹配的车
on that Jeep Wrangler that we like.
监控摄像头刚刚在罗斯伍德拍到了
POD cameras just got tripped up in Rosewood.
那好  去查吧
All right, let's get on it.
来
Come on.
我感谢你们照顾她
Hey, I appreciate you looking out for her.
我只是让她蹲下而已
I just pushed her to the curb.
你怎么知道有枪手
How'd you know it was coming?
我在阿富汗服役过
I was in Afghanistan.
-你会训练出这种反应  -你当过兵
- You get a feeling. - So, are you a soldier?
是
Used to be.
我非常尊重你们的付出
I respect all that y'all do.
你们不惜献出自己的生命
You know, you putting your life on the line
为了维护国家什么的
for your country and everything.
那样很好
That's legit.
哥们  我爱这个国家
Man, look, I love this country.
所以我才要下跪
You know, that's why I'm kneeling.
我想让这个国家更好
I wanna make it even better.
布里安娜  我们必须要问问
Brianna, we just have to ask,
你能不能想到任何人
is there anyone that you can think of
可能会想伤害你
that would wanna come after you?
任何和你有过节的
Anyone that has a grudge against you?
你是问我知不知道有谁想开枪打我
Like, do I know someone who would shoot me?
不知道
No.
我想和那帮杀害克里斯的新纳粹分子是一伙的
I assume it's the same Neo-nazis who went after Chris.
今天之前没有人对你发过威胁吗
Before today, no other specific threats?
没有
No.
那你呢  贾马尔  有人威胁你吗
What about you, Jamal? Any threats?
没有  有别的队伍因为下跪的事
No, I mean, other teams would talk trash
胡说过  不过
to us for kneeling, but...
弹道检测出来了
We got the ballistics.
人行道上的子弹和
Bullets in the drive-by are a match
杀死克里斯的子弹是匹配的
to the bullet that shot Chris.
那这个枪手可能也是迪克森
Dixon couldn't have been the shooter, then.
也可能是他下令的
He still could have ordered it.
-是  -也可能不是
- Yeah. - Or maybe not.
我们找到了那辆黑色牧马人
We found the Wrangler from the drive-by.
车辆识别代码被磨掉了
The VIN numbers were defaced,
霍斯特德给的那个车牌号
and the plates that Halstead gave us,
是从另一辆车偷来的
stolen off another vehicle.
有人想让这辆车消失
Somebody wanted this car to disappear.
上面还装了V8 LTI科尔维特发动机
Yeah, and it had a custom V8 LTI Corvette engine.
过去两年在本市只售出过112台
Only 112 of them were sold in this city the last two years.
只有三台装到了牧马人车上
Only three were installed in Wranglers.
其中一辆属于马科斯·布莱德利
And one of them belonged to Marcus Bradley.
哥伦比亚芝加哥学院的助理教练
The assistant coach of CCU.
去和他谈谈
Let's talk to him.
布莱德利教练
Coach Bradley.
多谢你花时间见我们
Thanks for taking the time.
队员们呢
Where's the team?
我们被暂停参加任何官方活动
We suspended all basketball activities.
球员们都在见悲伤咨询师
Players are meeting with the grief counselor.
是克里斯的事吗
This about Chris?
其实是你的事  你的车
Actually, it's about you. Your car.
2015款牧马人
2015 Wrangler.
那不是我的车了
That's not my car anymore.
我去年就卖了
I sold that last year.
卖了
Sold it?
你记得买家是谁吗
You remember the buyer?
不记得了
No, I don't.
不好意思  这事有什么关系吗
I'm sorry, but how is this pertinent?
当然有关系  因为你这辆牧马人
It is pertinent because your Wrangler was used
被用来偷袭枪击布里安娜·伍兹
in a drive-by shooting and the target was Brianna Woods.
-你认识她  -她写了那篇文章
- You know her? - She wrote that article
关于贾马尔和克里斯在国旗仪式上下跪的事
about Jamal and Chris protesting the anthem.
射向她的子弹
The bullets shot at her
和杀死克里斯的子弹是匹配的
matched the ones that killed Chris.
我不确定这事和我有什么关系
I'm not sure what this has to do with me.
车我已经卖了  如果还有问题
I sold that truck. Any further questions,
请去问我的律师
you can take it up with my lawyer.
追踪他的手机
Let's track his phone.
有电话接进来了
Call just went through.
-怎么了  教练  -K  还好吗
- What's up, Coach? - Yo, K, how's it going?
挺好的  出什么事了
It's all good. What's the problem?
警察他们知道车的事了
Yeah, the cops, they know about the car.
我们得保持距离了
We gotta keep our distance.
电话是打给肯德里克·盖恩斯的
All right, that call was made to a Kendrick Gaines.
我们对他了解多少
Yeah, what do we know about him?
没什么  就只有一些小量毒品问题
Oh, nothing much but some petty drug stuff.
我查到点东西
You know what? I got something.
克里斯高中的那项指控
Uh, the possession charge that Chris got in high school?
保释金是由肯德里克·盖恩斯出的
The bond was paid by Kendrick Gaines.
把他抓过来
Let's grab him up.
对了  打进去
There we go. Get in it.
强压  强压  强压
Press, press, press.
那是钱啊  犯规要罚钱的
That's money, man. That's foul money!
注意他的臀部  兄弟  注意他的臀部
Watch his hips, homie. Watch his hips!
拜托  强硬点
Come on, man! Be strong with the ball!
继续  兄弟  继续
Go ahead, man! Do that!
肯德里克·盖恩斯
Hey, hey. Kendrick Gaines?
是我
That's me.
在考察那个穿红短裤的小孩
Check out the kid in the red shorts.
小个子也能打篮球
Little man can ball.
你是球探
You a scout?
在非洲  他们挖钻石
Africa they dig for diamonds.
在野百
In the Wild Hundreds,
我们挖迈克尔·乔丹
we dig for Michael Jordans.
如果找到的话你能得到什么
What do you get if you find one?
满足感和免费的球票
Satisfaction and free tickets.
还有哥伦比亚芝加哥学院布莱德利教练的新吉普牧马人
And a new Jeep Wrangler from Coach Bradley from CCU.
你帮布莱德利教练招募的贾马尔和克里斯  是吗
You helped Coach Bradley recruit Jamal and Chris, right?
我的兄弟们想离家近些
My boys wanted to stay close to home.
对于克里斯来说也许太近了吧
Maybe too close for Chris, huh?
也许有的时候离家远点
I mean, maybe sometimes it's better to grow
能更好成长
away from your roots.
你们俩之间有过节吗
Y'all never had beef?
没有  我们关系不错
No, we were cool.
你们听我说
Hey, y'all go look,
我和发生的事无关
I ain't have nothing to do with what went down.
只是我们查了下通话记录
It's just that we checked the phone records,
克里斯在被杀之前打给的最后一个人
and the last person that Chris talked to before he was killed
是你
was you.
我总和我的兄弟们聊天
I talk to my boy all the time.
-只是巧合  -巧合
- It's just coincidence. - Coincidence?
昨天你的牧马人被用来飞车射击
Yesterday your Wrangler was used in a drive-by,
从车上射出的子弹
and the bullets that were shot from the vehicle
和杀了克里斯·泰勒的是一样的
were the same ones that killed Chris Taylor.
我发誓  我和这事无关
Look, on my soul, I had nothing to do with that.
我的车上周被偷了
My car got took last week.
那可真是太巧了
Well, that's incredibly convenient.
你上报了  对吗
You reported it, right?
好像芝加哥警察会优先处理似的
Like the CPD was gonna make it a top priority.
我对克里斯没兴趣
Look, I wasn't into it with Chris,
我的车被偷走了
and my car got took.
你们还想问什么
What else y'all want from me?
没了
I think we're good.
除非你有昨天早上的不在场证明
Unless you got alibi for yesterday morning.
我就在这和我的兄弟特雷在一起
I was right here with my boy, Trey.
-特雷  -是这样吗  特雷
- Trey? - That true, Trey?
你听到他说的了  朋友
You heard, folks.
特雷证明了
Trey confirms.
谢谢你的配合
Thank you for your time.
谢谢
Thank you.
小察察
Hey, Ops.
-小察察  -是在叫我们吗
- Ops! - Is that us?
-他妈的在逗我吗  -我觉得是
- You gotta be kidding. - I think so.
我很同情克里斯的遭遇
It's a shame what happened to Chris.
真的
For real.
他在撒谎
He lying his ass off.
是的
Yeah.
现在我们得证明他在撒谎
Now we just gotta prove it.
白人大学里的黑人小孩在国歌前下跪
Black kid at a white college kneels for the anthem.
为了他的信仰冒着被停学的危险
Risks suspension for something he believes in.
需要很大的勇气  我佩服他
Takes a lot of guts. I'll give him that.
你看到这个了吗
Did you see this?
去问问
Let's find out.
抱歉  布里安娜  我们得和你谈谈
I'm sorry, Brianna, we need to talk to you.
怎么了
Yeah, what is it?
你认识一个叫肯德里克·盖恩斯的家伙吗
Do you know a guy named Kendrick Gaines?
不认识  为什么这么问
No, doesn't ring a bell. Why?
你出现在他的脸书上
You're on his Facebook page.
你是怎么认识肯德里克·盖恩斯的
How do you know Kendrick Gaines?
我并不是很了解他
I don't really know him.
也许是在某个派对上见过
Maybe I saw him at some party.
我们查了你的电话
We checked your phone.
上个月你给他打了三次电话
You called him three times last month.
布里安娜  我是想帮你
Look, Brianna, I'm trying to help.
好吗
Okay?
你得和我说实话
You need to be honest with me.
你为什么给他打电话
Why'd you call him?
我只是想从他那弄点大麻
I was just trying to score some weed.
你是个大学生
You're a college student.
你不需要找野百的黑帮分子
You don't need a gangbanger from The Wild Hundreds
就能弄到大麻
to find pot.
宝贝  有人想杀你
Honey, someone just tried to kill you.
你得和我说实话
You need to be honest with me.
这是什么情况
What in the hell is going on in here?
-爸...  -你记得我和你说过什么吗
- Daddy... - Do you remember the talk?
丹尼  我们只是聊了聊
Denny, we're just having a conversation.
你记得我们说过什么吗
Do you remember the talk?
-当然记得  -不要逃避警察
- Of course I do. - You never run from a cop.
永远不要在律师不在场的时候和警察说话
You never talk to one without a lawyer.
-他是你朋友  -他是警察吗
- He's your friend. - Is he a cop?
我真是难以相信你不叫我就开始了
I can't believe you started without me.
丹尼...
Denny--
怎么回事  汉克
What is this really about, Hank, huh?
我只是想破了这个凶杀案
This is about me trying to solve a homicide
帮助你女儿
and trying to help your daughter.
仅此而已
Nothing more.
你问我  她和某个很难搞的人之间有问题
You ask me, she's in trouble with some very rough people.
一定和他男朋友贾马尔有关
Must be related to her boyfriend, Jamal.
肯定是这样
Comes straight from the hood.
目前我们知道的是她认识我们的头号嫌疑人
Well, all we've got so far is she knows our lead suspect.
一个叫肯德里克·盖恩斯的帮派分子
It's a gangbanger named Kendrick Gaines.
我们不知道他们是怎么认识的  为什么认识
We don't know how or why.
我和她聊聊
Let me talk to her.
我们能走了吗
Can we go now?
不能
No.
我们得弄明白真相
We need to get to some truth.
宝贝
Sweetheart.
你是理想主义者
You're an idealist.
你觉得你可以改变世界
You think you can change the world.
但我是警察  我看到的是黑暗
But I'm a cop. I see the darkness.
最令我恐惧的是...
And the only thing that scares me--
黑暗会找到你
The only thing is that the darkness will find you.
布里安娜  你就是我的命
Brianna, you are my life.
你现在有麻烦了
And you're in trouble.
但是你是怎么认识的肯德里克·盖恩斯
But how do you know Kendrick Gaines?
我只是想保护贾马尔
I was trying to protect Jamal.
这样他就能打篮球了
So he could play basketball.
好的  说吧  跟我说是什么情况
All right, go ahead. Just tell me what happened.
两个月前  我在贾马尔抽屉里发现很多现金
A couple months ago, I found lots of cash in Jamal's drawer.
我知道很可疑  所以就问他了
I knew it was suspicious, so I confronted him.
-毒资吗  -不是
- Drugs? - No.
-赌资  -什么意思
- Gambling. - What do you mean?
克里斯和贾马尔从小就开始
Chris and Jamal had been getting money from Kendrick
从肯德里克那里拿钱
since they were kids.
然后肯德里克想要回报
Then Kendrick wanted some payback.
想让他们打假球
Wanted them to shave points.
时不时地失误一下
You know, miss a few shots here and there.
我就知道我没看错贾马尔
I knew I was right about this Jamal.
不  这不是他的错  他也不想这么做
No, it's not his fault. He didn't want to do it.
他很害怕这会影响他做专业球员
He was scared it would hurt his chances of turning pro.
肯德里克威胁他
Kendrick threatened him.
所以我就打了个电话
That's why I called.
我没听懂
I'm not following.
我跟他说如果他再压榨贾马尔和克里斯
I told him if he didn't stop squeezing Jamal and Chris
我就告诉我父亲
that I was going to tell my father.
所以肯德里克想杀你
That's why Kendrick tried to shoot you.
我以为我可以处理这事
I thought I could handle this.
我不  我不知道  我
I didn't--I didn't know-- I--
是的
Yeah, well...
现在你知道了
Now you do.
真的是个噩梦
Man, this is a nightmare.
我最可怕的梦成真了
My worst dream is actually coming true.
打假球  你觉得还能怎么样
You were shaving points. What did you expect?
上一场没有  教练让我替补
Not the last game. Coach benched me.
其它比赛有没有拿钱
Took money for other games?
一点点
A few.
肯德里克从我十二岁时就开始给我钱
Kendrick has been giving me money since I was 12 years old.
那时我还年少无知
When I didn't know no better.
但一旦开始了  他就不会让你说停
Once you start, he don't let you stop.
肯德里克跟你和克里斯说打这场假球
And Kendrick told you and Chris to fix this game
-是两天前吗  -是的
- two nights ago? - That's right.
然后你知道如果你在唱国歌时跪下
And you knew the coach would bench you
教练就会让你替补
if you knelt during the anthem.
所以跪下就是你减少得分的方式吗
So taking a knee was your way of shaving points?
-不是  我们不是因为这个  -好吧
- No, that's not why we did it. - Okay.
我们准备上场的  确保我们能赢
We was gonna play, make sure we won.
不过是小比分赢
Just not by too many points.
那你为什么要跪下
Then why'd you take a knee?
因为布里安娜来了
Because Brianna showed up.
我以为她不会来
She wasn't even supposed to be there,
但我一看到她  我  我就不能放水了
but when I saw her, I...I couldn't back down.
我不能让她失望
You know? I couldn't let her down.
你跪下是因为布里安娜
All right, you took a knee for Brianna.
是的  这不是唯一的原因  但是...
Yeah. I mean, that wasn't the only reason, but...
在很多事情上她都让我开了眼界
She opened my mind to a lot of things.
那克里斯为什么跪下
All right, why'd Chris take a knee?
因为他是我朋友
Because he my friend.
我们永远共同进退
And we always had each other's back.
我以为这样也行
I thought it would still work.
我觉得如果我俩都不上场
You know, I figured we wouldn't score so much
我们就不会得很多分
if neither one of us played.
但这个新人  弗莱迪·莫斯利
But then this freshman, Freddy Mosely,
拿下了36分
goes off for 36 points.
这是他比赛生涯的最高分
Has the best game of his life.
肯德里克输了很多钱
Kendrick lost a lot of money.
他说我和克里斯必须要赔给他
He said me and Chris had to pay.
贾马尔
Look, Jamal,
我们可以帮你
we can help you.
你也一定要帮我们
You gotta help us.
你得戴上窃听器
We need you to wear a wire, man.
我们要让肯德里克亲口认罪
We gotta get a confession out of Kendrick.
你们已经知道是他杀了克里斯
You already know he killed Chris.
但我们没有证据
But we don't have proof.
肯德里克很聪明  没有留下线索
Kendrick was smart. Covered his tracks.
如果我戴窃听器
If I do this wire...
我还能继续打球  对吗
I get to go back to playing ball, right?
是的  贾马尔愿意合作
Yeah, Jamal's willing to cooperate,
但助理检察官很坚定
but the ASA is playing hardball.
-她给了什么条件  -没什么条件
- Well, what is she offering? - Not much.
赌博  再加上妨碍
Look, there's the gambling, plus obstruction,
还有私藏违禁品的前科
he's got a prior for possession.
她在力争送他进去
She's pushing for jail time.
我需要你帮忙挡回去
I need your help to push back.
是的  但如果助理检察官觉得入狱合适
Yeah, but if the ASA thinks jail time is appropriate,
我们应该尊重她的建议
we should honor her recommendation.
这都是可以协商的
Ah, Denny, it's all a negotiation.
-这你知道  -是的  但贾马尔犯法了
- You know that. - Yeah, well, Jamal broke the law.
我们在谈的是你女儿的男朋友
We're talking about your daughter's boyfriend.
男朋友总是会有的  汉克
Boyfriends come and go, Hank.
布里安娜在大学里跟一个来自野百的坏小子
Brianna was sowing a few wild oats in college
撒了一些种子
with a bad boy from the Wild Hundreds.
但现在我女儿该认真一点
But now it's time for my daughter to get serious
开启她人生的新篇章了
and start a new chapter in her life.
而贾马尔不属于这个新篇章
And Jamal will not be part of that chapter.
他进不去
He does not get a pass.
所以警长  我们要帮贾马尔争取交易吗
So Sarge, we gonna work out that deal for Jamal?
助理检察官在处理
The ASA's working on it.
好的  但你觉得应该可以  是吗
Okay, you think it's gonna happen, though?
我说了  助理检察官在处理
I said ASA is working on it.
好的
Okay.
贾马尔刚跟肯德里克聊过
Jamal just talked to Kendrick.
约了七点在乡绅酒吧的南边见面
The meet is set at Squire Lounge on the south side at 7.
我正在查那里的布局
I'm checking the layout out now.
有一个临街的入口  后面有一个出口
We've got one street entrance, one exit out the back.
安东尼奥和奥林斯基帮贾马尔装窃听器
Antonio and Olinsky are setting Jamal up with a wire.
我们一拿到肯德里克的认罪录音
As soon as we get Kendrick's confession,
就看我指示  抓他出来
on my signal, we scoop him up.
而且我们不能冒任何风险
And we're not taking any chances.
这家伙很危险
This guy is dangerous.
爸爸  我真的很感谢你做的一切
Dad, I really appreciate everything you've done.
你是我女儿啊  甜心
You're my daughter, sweetheart.
真高兴这事终于要结束了
I'm just so glad this is gonna be over.
贾马尔终于可以回篮球场  做职业球员
Jamal can finally get back to basketball and his career.
布里安娜  有些事情我想告诉你
Brianna, there's something that you need to know.
贾马尔回不去了
Jamal is not going to be able to come back from this.
什么意思
What do you mean?
打假球  这是体育场大忌
It's gambling. That's the one sin in sports
永远不会被原谅
that is never forgiven.
但我刚跟他聊过  他们跟他做了个交易
But I just talked to him. They gave him a deal.
他们说如果他配合
They said if he just cooperated--
他可能可以不用进监狱  有可能
He might avoid jail time. He might.
如果他运气好的话
If he's lucky.
现在你该别再为贾马尔担心了
It's time for you to stop worrying about Jamal
专心管好自己  过好你的人生
and focus on yourself. On your life.
你说什么
Excuse me?
贾马尔的人生轨迹和你的人生轨迹
Jamal's path and your path
通向完全不同的两个方向
are going in completely different directions.
你是一个非常出色的年轻女性
You are an extraordinary young woman,
总有一天你会遇到一个配得上你的男人
and one day you'll find a man who deserves you.
你觉得贾马尔配不上我吗
And you don't think Jamal deserves me?
因为他在唱国歌时跪下了吗
Because he kneeled for the national anthem?
-布里安娜  -站着对你来说这么重要吗
- Brianna-- - Taking a stand bothers you that much?
这当然惹恼我了
Of course it bothers me.
我是警察  而他向我抗议
I'm a cop. He was protesting me.
不  他是抗议种族歧视
No, he was protesting racism.
他对我竖起了中指
He was giving me the middle finger.
布里安娜
Brianna...
我认识你比你了解自己还久
I have known you longer than you've known yourself.
我了解你的内心  而这些你还尚待探索
I know things about your heart you have yet to discover.
宝贝  他不是你对的人
Sweetheart, he's wrong for you.
你是说他来自
You mean because he comes from
城市里出身不好的地方
the wrong part of the city?
还是他有纹身
Or has tattoos?
还是他的黑皮肤不对吗
Or he's the wrong kind of black?
不只是这样
There's more to it than just that.
布里安娜
Brianna...
Brianna!
布里安娜
Brianna--
你还好吗
You all right?
你看上去有点心不在焉
You seem a little distracted.
是啊  宾汉姆的事
Yeah, it's this Bingham thing.
伍兹说他们在尸体内发现了一颗子弹
Woods said they found a slug in the body.
所以
So?
他们查到枪支注册在5年前
They traced it back to a gun registered to this punk
我逮捕的一个混混名下
I pinched five years ago.
而枪没有收回过
Never recovered the gun.
所以我成了嫌疑人
Makes me a suspect.
-他在唬你  -不是
- He's bluffing. - No, he's not.
他是冲着我来的  老埃
He's coming after me, Al.
我以为你俩休战了
I thought you two had a truce?
对  但没休多久
Yeah, well, it ain't gonna last.
他太想抓住我把柄了
He wants me too bad.
听好
All right, listen up.
嫌犯在地点出现  和另一名男性一起
Suspect is on location. He's with another male.
非裔美国人  穿蓝色大衣
African American, blue coat.
我不确定我能不能做到  老兄
I don't know if I can do this, man.
我觉得我可能得和律师聊聊
I think maybe I need to be talking to a lawyer.
谁在一直轰炸你的手机
Who's blowing up your phone?
肯德里克
Yo, Kendrick.
-你想聊聊  -是的
- You wanted to talk. - Yeah.
事情是这样  自从克里斯被杀
Look, the thing is, ever since Chris got killed,
就有很多条子找我
there's been a lot of police around.
你告诉他们什么了
And what'd you tell them?
-什么都没说  -那就对了
- Nothing. - That's right.
什么都别告诉他们
Nothing for them to know.
你唯一要操心的就是把我丢的钱
The only thing you gotta worry about is getting me back
弄回来
that money I lost.
老兄  我不能一直这么干
Bro, I can't keep doing that.
我一直打这种坏比赛  前途就毁了
I keep throwing up bad games, it's gonna kill my career.
什么意思
What?
你还是觉得你要去NBA
You still think you're going to the NBA?
不可能了
That is no longer happening.
-我还有机会  -有过机会
- I still got a shot. - Had a shot.
但你还是新人的时候你的膝盖伤
But that knee injury you got when you were a freshman,
就让你失去了半步机会
you lost half a step.
半步  那是
Half a step, that's--
那意味着离NBA有100英里了
That's 100 miles in the NBA.
-那是假的  -不幸  这是真的
- That's--that's a lie. - Sadly, it's the truth.
等这一切都结束  兄弟  我就是你的依靠
And when all this is over, my brother, i'm all you got left.
所以
So.
你凭什么觉得可以糊弄我
Why'd you think you could play me?
兄弟  我没有
Bro, I didn't--
弗莱迪·莫斯利拿了36分
Freddy Mosley went off for 36 points.
究竟谁能料想到这种事发生
Who in the world could have saw that happening?
这就是上帝之举
That was a act of God.
你和克里斯就该控制比赛
You and Chris were supposed to control that game.
然后你们就跪着唱国歌
And then you knelt for the anthem
乖乖坐板凳上
and got your dumb asses benched.
最后我们才这样了
And here we are.
所以你除掉克里斯吗
Is that why you took Chris out?
我喜欢克里斯
I liked Chris.
我本不想这样的
I didn't want it to go down the way it did.
我告诉他  他欠我钱
I went to tell him he owed me money.
他去抢我的枪  然后
He reached for my gun, and it just went...
走火了
Off.
你不会想做克里斯这样的傻子
You don't wanna be a fool like Chris.
好了  他招了
All right, we got it.
-准备进去  -汉克  等等
- Let's prepare to move in. - Oh, Hank, hold on, hold on.
那是伍兹的女儿
That's Woods' daughter.
她在这干嘛
What is she doing here?
安东尼奥  我们有情况了
Antonio, we got a situation.
收到我短信了吗
Did you get my text?
你来这干嘛  布里安娜
What you doing here, Brianna?
我来见贾马尔喝一杯
I just came to meet Jamal for a drink.
我不知道他和你一起
I didn't know he was with you.
布里安娜  你还好吗
Brianna, hey. How you doing?
-我们离开这  -慢着  慢着
- Let's you and me get outta here. - Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
你又是谁
Who the hell are you?
我让他供认了  抓住他
Yo, I got the confession! Arrest him!
站住  站住
Hey, man! Hey, hey, hey!
举起手
Hands! Hands!
你是该死的条子
You're the damn police!
-放松  -举起手
- Take it easy. - Let's see some hands.
-举起手  -好
- Put your hands up! - All right.
-举手  -好
- Put them up! - Okay.
以我所爱起誓  你最好别动
On everything I love, you better not move.
他们把窃听器放哪儿了
Where'd they put the wire?
伙计  不是这样的
Guys, it ain't like that, bro.
他们把窃听器放哪儿了
Hey, man, where'd they put the wire?
放地上
On the ground.
布里安娜和这事没关系  兄弟
Bro, Brianna ain't got nothing to do with this, brother--
坐下
Sit down!
别动  坐好
Don't move! In the chair!
谁都不许离开
Nobody leaves. Nobody.
我听说了  布里安娜
I got word. Brianna?
她在里面
She's inside.
怎么会这样的
How in the hell did that happen?
-你告诉我啊  -错误的时间和地点
- You tell me. - Wrong time, wrong place.
丹尼  她很清楚发生了什么事
Denny, she knew exactly what was going down,
而且不是我们告诉她的
and she didn't get it from us.
我告诉了布里安娜可能会发生什么
I told Brianna what was likely to happen
在贾马尔合作之后
after Jamal cooperated.
也许他打给她告诉自己在哪
Maybe he called her and told her where he was.
她过来试着劝他
She came down here trying to talk him out of it.
她搞砸了我们的行动
She blew up our operation.
别怪她身上  汉克
Don't put it on her, Hank!
不是我想怪她的
That's not where I'm putting it.
怎么救她出来
How do we get her out?
安东尼奥在里面
I got Antonio inside.
看到条子了  很糟
Seeing blue. This is bad, G.
冷静  兄弟
Hey, just chill, man.
我能搞定
I got this.
你搞不定
No, you don't got this.
我跟你说过闭嘴了
You know, I have told you to shut up, man.
肯德里克
Kendrick.
你话太多了
You talk too much, man.
听我说
Listen to me.
想活命吗
You wanna live?
那就跟我合作
Work with me.
我是你的出路
I'm your way out.
外面有很多白人警察
There's a lot of white police officers out there
蓄势待发向你开枪
with itchy trigger fingers waiting to shoot you.
你走不了多远
You won't make it 2 feet.
让我给我的警长打电话
Let me call my Sergeant.
现在谈话是你最好的武器
Talking's the best weapon you got right now.
不不不
No, no, no.
-她才是最好的武器  -不
- She's the best weapon I got. - No!
-过来  -布里安娜
- Now. - Brianna!
-不  -丹尼
- No! - Denny.
-我要进去  -不行
- I'm going in. - No, you can't!
给我让开  我女儿在里面
Get the hell out of my way! My daughter is in there!
丹尼  里面有15个人
Denny, there's 15 people in there!
你拿着枪冲进去  肯定会是血流成河
You march in with a gun, it's gonna be a bloodbath.
马上把你的手拿开
Get your hands off me right now.
-这是命令  -老大
- That's an order. - Boss, boss--
我们不能在这里干等着
Look, we're not gonna just sit here!
丹尼  你得信任我
Denny! You've got to trust me!
里面有我的人
I've got a man inside!
等等
Just hold on.
说话  安东尼奥
Talk to me, Antonio.
不  不是安东尼奥
No, this ain't Antonio.
我是肯德里克
This is Kendrick.
我跟你说明白  现在我说了算
And just so we're clear, I'm in charge.
-明白吗  -明白
- You feel me? - I feel you.
但我的任务是确保大家都活着
But it's my job to make sure everybody in there stays alive.
你放下武器  一切就会和平结束
You lay down your weapons, this all ends peacefully.
和平  不可能
Peace? That's dead.
我这里有一个条子  一个条子的女儿
I got a cop, and I got the daughter of a cop.
我只想要自由
I just want freedom.
是吗  你释放人质
Yeah? You release those hostages,
我就能帮你得到
I can help you get it.
帮我  我不需要你的帮助
Help? I don't need your help.
你需要我的帮助
You need my help.
你需要我的帮助来保证这些人活着
You need my help to keep these people alive.
你说
I'm listening.
好
Good.
我要你们都走
I want y'all to clear out.
走得远远的
Miles away.
我要一辆加满油的车
And I want a car with a full tank of gas.
可以
I can get that.
但你和你的朋友要单独上车  肯德里克
But you and your friend gotta get in that car alone, Kendrick.
只有这样你提的条件才可行
That's the only way this thing works.
明白吗
You feel me?
随便
Whatever, man.
把车给我就行
Just get me the car.
你听到他说的了
All right, you heard him.
你女儿在里面
Look, it's your daughter in there.
你想怎么做我都听你的
I'll do whatever you want.
我们可以现在冲进去
We can move in right now.
把车给他
Get him the car.
安心等着
Hang tight.
就快结束了
It's almost over.
你没事吧
You all right?
我没事
I'm good.
亲爱的
Baby...
真的对不起  是我把你牵扯进来的
I am so sorry for bringing you into all of this.
-我为发生的一切向你道歉  -不  是我的错
- I'm sorry for everything. - No, it's my fault.
我不知道肯德里克会在这里
I didn't know Kendrick would be here.
你一起来
You're coming with.
不许多嘴  兄弟
One more word, Mally Mal.
不许多嘴
One more word.
你就是个傻子  你知道吗
You're a damn fool, you know that?
我们曾那么铁
We had something special, man.
我照顾了你
I took care of you.
-你照顾的是你自己  -走
- You took care of yourself. - Let's go.
他们肯定不会同意
No way they agreed to this.
我不会什么保护措施都没有就出去
Hey, I ain't going out there without protection.
快走  闭嘴
So let's go, and shut up.
事实上
Matter of fact,
贾马尔  你给我滚去卫生间
Mal, get your goof ass in the bathroom.
大家都进卫生间
Everybody in the bathroom right now!
都想中枪吗  马上进卫生间
Y'all wanna get hit? Get in the bathroom right now!
看着我  不要想跑
Look at me. Don't try to run.
一定不要妄动  听到了吗
Stay perfectly still. You hear me?
千万不要跑
Don't try to run.
开门
Open the door.
走  开门
Come on, let's go. Open the door.
放松  慢点
Relax. Slow.
不能让她上那辆车
You cannot let her get into that car.
不会的
I won't.
说话  杰
Talk to me, Jay.
无法开枪  警长
No shot, Sarge.
-不要动了  -爸爸  你在吗
- Stop moving. - Dad, are you there?
布里安娜  冷静
Brianna, just stay calm.
他们怎么说你就怎么做
Do what they say.
不
No!
布里安娜
Brianna!
宝贝
Hey, baby.
开辆警车来
Get a squad car!
得马上送她去医院
We gotta get her to the hospital right away now!
收到
Copy that.
亲爱的  坚持住
Come on, baby. Just stay with me.
亲爱的  坚持
Come on, baby. Come on.
有我们在
We got you. Come on.
挺住
Come on. Come on.
挺住  乖女儿  乖女儿
Come on, that's my girl. That's my girl.
乖女儿
That's my girl. Yes.
布里安娜怎么样了
How's Brianna?
我想见她
I wanna see her.
回家吧  孩子
Go home, son.
什么意思
What you mean?
意思是你见不到她
It means you're not going to see her.
-我是她男朋友  -你不是
- I'm her boyfriend. - No, you're not.
我让你回家
I said go home.
警官  这个人在引发骚乱
Officer, this man is causing a disturbance.
没有  你不能这样
Hell, no. You can't do that, man.
把他带走
Remove him.
-什么  我...  -走
- What--I just- - Come on.
-走  -要这样吗
- Let's go. - Yeah?
走
Let's go!
你不能...别推我了
You can't-bro, stop shoving me.
走
Let's go!
他怎么样了
How is she?
情况不好  汉克
She's not good, Hank.
她快不行了
She's dying.
真的很遗憾  丹尼
I'm so sorry, Denny.
我们尽力了
We did everything we could.
嗯
Yeah.
可是
Well...
还是不够
It wasn't good enough.